One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud.
Always stand up! Raise our unyielding flag.
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward! Hands up!!
"I'm almost there, just a little further and I'll have the answer."
That's what I believed as I sailed into this new world.
That's right, the pieces of our dreams are joined together as one.
We're connected by unwavering bonds, let's head for a bright future!
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud.
Always stand up! Raise our unyielding flag.
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward!
Always look up!
Keep your head held high!
Always step up!
Fly over the waves!
Our dreams have been carefully joined together.
Now let's head for the future!
We drift forward, riding the waves,
meeting people and saying goodbye, then doing it again,
all under this flag...
Pain I don't want to forget is kept in my heart.
There was a day when I softly carved it there.
I won't let anyone take my freedom.
I grasp it tightly in my hands!
Now raise your hands up! Sing your dreams out loud.
Always stand up! Raise our unyielding flag.
So many obstacles are already behind us!
Now let's keep moving forward!
Always look up!
Keep your head held high!
Always step up!
Fly over the waves!
Our dreams have been carefully joined together.
Now let's head for the future!
Zoro's Strongest One-Sword Style
and Mocha's Plight!
Alright! Let's go, G-5!
Obey Captain-chan! Move your asses and save the kids!
I thought Caesar was the only Logia here.
We don't stand a chance against her.
Black Leg bro, why didn't you help us when she attacked?
Don't be spoiled brats. I would never kick a woman!
What if a woman was going to kill you?
Then I choose death.
That's just crazy!
There's all kinds of people in your crew, isn't there?
Yeah, Pirate Hunter bro looked like he was attacking her without mercy.
He's actually quite the softy, but he'll get the job done.
We can leave it to him.
We don't have to worry about Tashigi-chan, either.
Anyway...
Nami-san, Robin-chan and Tashigi-chan will praise us...
if we go save those damn brats!
Yeah!
Biscuits Room
In Front of the Exit
You should get out of here too.
I'm free to do what I want.
I'm saying that you're in the way!
You're free to believe whatever you want.
Okay, then...
Is a pirate like me free to cut you down first, female marine?
I don't think so.
You're not going to cut me down.
And you're not going to cut her down, either.
You don't know that!
I was thinking the same thing.
It must be true.
Why won't you finish the job?!
Is it because I'm a woman?!
I can't stand the fact that you exist!
Listen! It's that face of yours!
It looks exactly like my friend's who died a long time ago!
And now you're even saying the same things she said!
Quit imitating her, you copycat!
What a childish thing to say!
You think women are weak, so you don't use your full strength, and won't finish them off!
You might not lose, but you can't win either!
That's why I stayed here!
If this Logia user went after my subordinates, the casualties would be enormous!
Are you mocking me?!
Yes.
Do whatever you want.
It was my job to stop this woman from attacking my comrades, as well.
So as long as this corridor is protected there's no problem.
How can you be so carefree?
We're running out of time. You should run as well!
Don't let your guard down.
The enemy's trying to kill you.
That's right!
Thank you for telling me his weakness.
You may be able to use a little Haki but my bite will still kill you easily!
How annoying!
But even if Haki lets you wound a Logia,
it won't mean anything if I'm too fast for you to catch me.
Isn't that right?!
You're a cold man.
I don't want to hear that from a snow woman.
Don't look away!
Do you like snowball fights?
Snow Rabbit!
Shave!
You are Smoker's right hand woman.
Perhaps I underestimated you.
Blizzard!
Hey, hey.
I'll be sure to let your subordinates know...
all about your pathetic death.
What's happened to my shoulder?!
What are you doing?!
Let go of me!
If I let go, she'll rip my shoulder off.
I can just crush your shoulder, if you prefer!
For all your boasting, you're sure taking a long time to finish this.
You're out of time.
I'm heading on ahead.
I thought that he wouldn't attack a woman...
but he just attacked with the intent to hurt me!
You really underestimated me, snow-woman.
You should have run away earlier...
when you realized that you couldn't defeat me.
There are some things that I don't want to slice up.
But...
have you ever met a wild beast who promised that they wouldn't bite?
Because I haven't.
W-What is this?!
My body won't move!
One Sword Style...
He's going to cut me down!
Great Dragon Shock!
Are you two satisfied now?
He cut her!
Are you... mocking me?!
She's still alive!
Don't tell me he didn't use Haki?
She can't control her own body.
She knows she'd have died if he had used Haki, and she's overwhelmed by fear of his strength.
I've never seen someone win a fight like this.
What could the Straw Hat Crew have been doing for the past two years while they were hiding?
Just how strong have they become?
I won't let you escape!
Cutting Autumn Rain!
You have lost this fight!
What was the meaning of that?
You didn't deliver the finishing blow.
It's just like I said, you think-
You butted in, so you can't talk.
If you hadn't done it then I would have.
Stop lying! You're only saying that because I've already done it.
Your help was not needed.
Well...
Good job Captain Glasses. You didn't let her go after anyone.
You can have all the credit.
Why do you always talk like you're superior to me?
Because you're inferior to me.
Mocha! Give us the candy!
Lady!
Now let's go!
Let go of me! What are you doing?!
Stay still. I'm giving you a sedative.
Huh? Where am I?
This won't stop us!
Oh no! We have to chase after the kids!
Alright.
Give us the candy!
Wait!
Milky Ball!
Not again!
This isn't going to work forever.
How long do I have to hold them off?!
What is this place?
I don't know which way to go anymore!
Biscuits Room Winner: Zoro
10 minutes until Shinokuni fills up building B
The killer gas is leaking into the Biscuits Room?
What now?!
This isn't the way to the exit!
Please put me down before we catch up to my men.
Why are you always so prideful?
Do you want me to drop you right now?!
What now?!
Isn't this the legendary named sword, Shuusui?!
Shuusui: Clear Autumn Water
Don't touch it!
Just shut up and let me carry you, you sword geek!
No!
Mocha?
Konbu, Biyo, stop it! Please listen to me!
Mocha!
Oh no! Some of the children cut her off!
This is terrible! If they get the candy, they'll fall right back into their addiction!
We have to get those kids away from Mocha!
I wanna go home!
Mocha ate all of it!
Mocha!
How could she be so stupid?
Give it back, Mocha!
You gotta be kidding me!
Don't hog it all, you idiot!
Mocha!
Don't do it! Spit it all out!
Mocha, can you hear me?!
Mocha!
I told you what that drug was, didn't I?!
Chopper-chan.
They're all...
my friends!
Don't do it!
I promise!
Once we grow up...
When we're all grown up, we should go out to sea.
The sea?
You mean become fishermen?
Don't be stupid, I mean we should go on an adventure.
Let's go find stuff like islands made of gold!
Sounds fun!
Once we've recovered and we go back to our islands,
we'll all be apart.
If we go out to sea when we grow up, we can meet up again.
Oh, I see. Great! I don't want to leave my friends.
So when are we gonna go?
Hmmm, how about...
When we turn twenty!
That's so far off.
That'll just make it more exciting, right?
I see!
Then let's promise!
So, Master is a bad guy?
Yeah. He's as bad as they come.
But he's always so nice to us.
The candy he gives us every day is so tasty!
It's all part of his trap.
No way, but...
You're... his test subjects.
T-Test subjects?
Mocha, open the door!
We're going to Biscuits Room!
You were never really sick!
T-That's impo-
Your big bodies are proof.
Turning humans into giants as a tool of war...
is something scientists all around the world have been trying to do for centuries.
In other words, their experiments have failed over and over for centuries. Nobody has succeeded.
There's no easy way to say this...
This experiment...
will also fail.
Caesar knows this. All he cares about is gathering data for his next experiment.
So... what's gonna happen to us?
You'll die. None of you will make it home.
That delicious candy is a lethal poison.
It causes your body to break down without you even realizing it!
And yet, if you eat one you'll want another.
The more you eat, the harder it'll be to escape from Caesar's grip!
When you saw the children on the other side of this door, you could see how terrifying it is, right?
I've given you a sedative, but the side effects of the candy and the experiments...
will most likely...
claim your life long before you grow up.
Mocha!
We won't grow up?
We... won't ever get to see our moms and dads again?
That's right. Not unless we get you out of here now.
We never thought that we could die.
We wanted him to help us because we wanted to go home!
We were afraid he might break his promise and keep us for another year because of the unknown disease!
But...
We didn't think we were gonna die!
We thought we were going to grow up!
This isn't what they promised us!
We only ate the candy because they gave it to us!
Nobody thought they were going to die!
I know! You've done nothing wrong!
That's why we're gonna get Caesar, no matter what!
I can't forgive him!
I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry... that we didn't find you sooner!
Chopper-chan, we...
don't want to die!
I won't let you die!
I swear I'll save you!
Caesar is a strong, evil, terrifying man...
but, you know...
our captain is much stronger!
He'll be the king of these seas someday!
Luffy will definitely beat Caesar!
So listen up... Mocha, right?
We can't let the other kids have the candy, ever again.
I'm going to stay here and do my best to give them the sedative.
So Mocha, will you go to the Biscuits Room and protect the candy there?
Yeah!
I understand! I'll never let them eat the candy again!
We're all going to go home together!
Exactly!
Mocha just coughed up blood!
Why'd the delicious candy make her do that?
I can't believe this!
The children have stopped.
See? This is because you were so selfish!
Why?
This is what the candy does to you!
Mocha wanted to save you!
Even if it meant... sacrificing herself!
Chopper, this might be our only chance to calm them down!
But I have to treat Mocha first!
There's no time.
The kids are standing still!
Go!
No violence, alright guys?!
Yeah!
Fight numbers with numbers!
Hold them down!
Alright!
Sanji-kun?!
The Navy?!
Bro! Does kicking them in the balls count as violence?
It's a little over the line.
Roger that!
Medical team, up front!
Yes, Sir!
Chopper, let these guys help you!
They can handle an injection or two, at least!
Right!
Alright, you're gonna hafta calm down now!
Forward!
I'm pretty sure the examination room is around here somewhere.
Carry her there!
She doesn't have long. You know that, right, Racoon Dog?
I know!
Mocha...
Dammit, this is my fault!
Chopper-chan...
Mocha, are you alright?
I...
I didn't give them the candy!
Yeah! You protected your friends!
Thank you.
Thank you!
Thanks to you, everyone can go home!
Mocha, I promise I'll save you too!
I swear...
you will grow up!
Thanks!
Building C - Dust Box
What?!
Straw Hat Luffy!
Where is Caesar?
H-He's right down this corridor, in Building R!
I see.
I got it.